(Sheldon:)I know Hawking's not busy,
because I can see...
(Sheldon:)...he's playing other people right now.
(Leonard:)Maybe since you're so good,
he's taking his time to meet the challenge.
(Leonard:)- I want Penny to enjoy...
- Wolowitz told me he's a big baby.
Yeah, I didn't know that,
and I played "extract" for 82 points.
Oh, it's all Amy's fault.
She told me to play it.
(Sheldon:)I have got to cut her loose.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I wasn't done talking.
(Leonard:)She hands in the paper tomorrow.
I know I could help her.
(Leonard:)And she's my girlfriend.
I should be allowed to help her.
(Leonard:)- Why aren't I allowed to help her?
- I hear you, brother.
(Leonard:)No, you need to give me some advice.
Uh, fine. Women, huh?
(Leonard:)Specific to my situation.
Blond women, huh?
- Empathetic.
- Sucks to be you.
I quit!
(Sheldon:)Leonard, wait, no.
I listened to your dumb thing.